{
    "subject": "resource/Berkeley_Preparatory_School",
    "predicate": "ontology/mascot",
    "object": "Buccaneers",
    "human_readable": "The mascot of Berkeley Preparatory School is Buccaneers.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.937874972820282,
            "question": "Is there a mascot associated with Berkeley Preparatory School?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9204305410385132,
            "question": "Why do you think Berkeley Preparatory School chose a Buccaneers mascot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9060837030410767,
            "question": "What is the mascot of Berkeley Preparatory School?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8240386247634888,
            "question": "Who or what is the mascot for Berkeley Prep?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6886963248252869,
            "question": "What animal represents Berkeley Preparatory School?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6732234358787537,
            "question": "If you were to design merchandise for Berkeley Preparatory School, what imagery would you use based on the mascot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6681734323501587,
            "question": "How might the mascot influence school spirit at Berkeley Preparatory School?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5798956155776978,
            "question": "What are some common symbols associated with the Buccaneers mascot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35380250215530396,
            "question": "Can you think of other schools with similar mascots?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24257445335388184,
            "question": "What nickname do students and alumni use for their school based on its mascot?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The mascot of Berkeley Preparatory School is Buccaneers.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4786_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you think of other schools with similar mascots?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4786_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common symbols associated with the Buccaneers mascot?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4786_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How might the mascot influence school spirit at Berkeley Preparatory School?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4786_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4786_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4786_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4786_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4786_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4786_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4786_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4786_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4786_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4786_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4786_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents multiple times confirm that the mascot of Berkeley Preparatory School is the Buccaneers. For instance, both `37.txt` and `21.txt` explicitly state this fact. Therefore, the statement \"The mascot of Berkeley Preparatory School is Buccaneers\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}